[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When were the 107 episodes of the American sitcom My Favorite Martian first aired?", "correct_answer": "In the 1960s", "incorrect_answers": ["In the 1980s", "In the 1990s", "In the 1950s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Matt Groening, the creator of The Simpsons, grew up on a street named what?", "correct_answer": "Evergreen Terrace", "incorrect_answers": ["Main Street", "Springfield Boulevard", "Simpson Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charles Bronson, Claudia Cardinale and Henry Fonda starred in this western movie from 1968.", "correct_answer": "Once Upon a Time in the West", "incorrect_answers": ["Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "The Treasure of the Sierra Madre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fictional characters is known for wearing a top hat all the time?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mad Hatter", "Willy Wonka", "The Penguin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the condition of having a unibrow called?", "correct_answer": "Synophrys", "incorrect_answers": ["Monobrowphism", "Uniphys", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "My baby takes the morning train, he works from nine till five and then \nHe takes another home again to find me waitin for him\nWhich artist sings this early 80s hit, My Baby Takes The Morning Train?", "correct_answer": "Sheena Easton", "incorrect_answers": ["Alana Miles", "Stacy Lattisaw", "Moby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Broccoli looks very similar to this vegetable and is often confused with it.", "correct_answer": "Cauliflower", "incorrect_answers": ["Brussels sprouts", "Lettuce", "Cabbage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the atomic number of the atom define?", "correct_answer": "Its number of protons", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Its electrical charge", "Its number of isotopes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is not the alcohol in wine that causes hangover.  Hangover is actually caused by these.", "correct_answer": "Impurities", "incorrect_answers": ["Antioxidants", "Polyphenols", "Carbides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This distillery, founded in 1608 in a small village in Northern Ireland, is the oldest licenced whiskey distillery in the world.", "correct_answer": "Old Bushmills Distillery", "incorrect_answers": ["Cooley Distillery", "Tullamore Distillery", "Heaven Hill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The telephone handset has two main parts. One is the mouthpiece or transmitter. What is the other one?", "correct_answer": "receiver", "incorrect_answers": ["telephone wire", "numbers", "handpiece"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Pretty in Pink, Andie\u2019s love interest finally makes the big move on her. How does he make it?", "correct_answer": "By chatting in the computer lab", "incorrect_answers": ["By sending a message through a friend", "By calling her on the phone", "By writing her a letter"]}]